Interviewer: Hi, Sandra. Tell us a bit about your experience.
Where are you working?
Sandra: I’m working in a clothes shop called FatFace.
Interviewer: What kind of clothes does FatFace have?
Sandra: Er, well, clothes for men and women, informal clothes, trousers, T-shirts, sweaters, things like that.
Interviewer: What do you do every day?
Sandra: Well, er, I help the customers to find the clothes that they’re looking for.
It’s a big shop and it has a lot of things. People sometimes can’t see the things that they want.
Interviewer: Do you like working there?
Sandra: Yes, I love it. The people are really nice to me. I’m making a lot of new friends.
Interviewer: Is there anything you don’t like?
Sandra: Well, we can’t sit down, we’re standing up all the time. So that’s quite hard.
Interviewer: But, in general, you’re happy?
Sandra: Oh, yes. And when my two weeks finish they say I can work here on Saturdays!
That’s great for me. I really like working in a clothes shop.
Interviewer: What do you wear at work?
Sandra: We wear clothes from the shop.
Interviewer: Are the clothes that you’re wearing today from FatFace?
Sandra: Yes, they are!